Richard Hodgson

Curriculum Vitae

Personal Details

Full name Richard Anthony Hodgson

Date of Birth 8th May 1984 Nationality British Citizen

Permanent Address

11 Rushey Gill Brandon Durham County Durham DH7 8BL

Contact Details

Mobile Number 07709 342362

Email Address contact@rhodgson.co.uk

Qualifications

Qualification	Subject	Grade
GCSE	English Language English Literature Mathematics Double Award Science Drama Graphic Products German Art	B C CC B C D
BTEC National Diploma	Computer Studies	2 Distinctions 2 Merits 4 Passes
Keyskills	Application of Number Information Technology	Pass Pass
ECDL		Pass
Degree (BSc.)	Web Development	Second Class Honours (2 nd Division)

Employment History

August 2004 ~ September 2005

Full-time Employment as Web Developer DfES Pathfinder Project - Fit4Employment (Placement)

September 2005 ~ June 2006

Consultancy (Web focused / Intranet orientated)
Durham Community Business College

July 2006 ~ Present

Full-time Employment as Web Developer Durham Federation (Durham Community Business College & Fyndoune Community College)

References

Mrs A Lakey (Head Teacher)

Durham Community Business College Bracken Court Ushaw Moor Durham

DH7 7NG

Mr P Robinson

5 Thornbury Rise Darlington

DL3 9NE

Personal Statement

From the age of 10 I have always expressed an interest in computing and related subjects. It has allowed me to demonstrate my ability to analyse and quickly understand systems varying in complexity. Because of this interest in computing, and specifically web based technologies, I have always felt self driven to develop my skills further and learn from my experiences. I like being thanked for producing high quality solutions and this in itself motivates me.

I have been learning to make websites for nearly a decade now. It has grown from an idle hobby to a marketable skill; one that can make a valuable contribution to industry. I have also developed a good understanding of project management, constantly gaining experience working in a variety of teams.

When I'm not planning, developing or talking about websites, I enjoy watching anything by Simon Pegg, attempting to mix on my record decks or simply relaxing and socialising with friends.

I have also be known to juggle, ride my bike, go paint balling, cook and build large sound systems.

Further information and examples of my work can be found at http://www.rhodgson.co.uk.